[{
    "question": "Where was the ancient origin of tennis created?",
    "choice1": "France",
    "choice2": "British Empire",
    "choice3": "Argentina",
    "choice4": "Spain",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "When did people start using rackets for tennis?",
    "choice1": "15th Century",
    "choice2": "16th Century",
    "choice3": "17th Century",
    "choice4": "18th Century",
    "answer": 2
}, {
    "question": "Which female has won the most Grand Slam tournaments?",
    "choice1": "Serena Williams",
    "choice2": "Maria Sharapova",
    "choice3": "Margaret Court",
    "choice4": "Monica Seles",
    "answer": 3
}, {
    "question": "The French Open tournament is played on which surface?",
    "choice1": "Grass",
    "choice2": "Clay",
    "choice3": "Gravel",
    "choice4": "Flexible",
    "answer": 2
}, {
    "question": "In tennis, how many point(s) does “love” mean?",
    "choice1": "40",
    "choice2": "30",
    "choice3": "15",
    "choice4": "0",
    "answer": 4
}, {
    "question": "Roger Federer comes from which nation?",
    "choice1": "Sweden",
    "choice2": "France",
    "choice3": "Spain",
    "choice4": "Switzerland",
    "answer": 4
}, {
    "question": "Which material was the first tennis racket string made of?",
    "choice1": "Steel",
    "choice2": "Sheep gut",
    "choice3": "Plastic",
    "choice4": "Cotton",
    "answer": 2
}, {
    "question": "Which Grand Slam tournament has the longest history?",
    "choice1": "The U.S. Open",
    "choice2": "The Australian Open",
    "choice3": "Roland Garos",
    "choice4": "Wimbledon",
    "answer": 4
}, {
    "question": "Which male player made 8 consecutive finals at the U.S. Open?",
    "choice1": "Rafael Nadal",
    "choice2": "Novak Djokovic",
    "choice3": "Ivan Lendl",
    "choice4": "Andre Agassi",
    "answer": 4
}, {
    "question": "What does an ace mean?",
    "choice1": "A trick shot",
    "choice2": "A ball not returned by the opponent",
    "choice3": "A serve hitting the opponent’s legs",
    "choice4": "A winning game point",
    "answer": 2
}, {
    "question": "Which gas is filled in the hollow cores of a pressurized tennis ball?",
    "choice1": "Hydrogen",
    "choice2": "Nitrogen",
    "choice3": "Oxygen",
    "choice4": "Carbon",
    "answer": 2
}]